[{"topicId":"8","id":"8000","langCode":"vi","question":"qkmdlejPLtklS+14r10dzlJ+4DS61XYieiCFjVqB85pxzdhZr6F85vnFVc/Nq4Uk","answers":["take over","take care of","account for","give up"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5KuZ9De0q/hu10Cwx2sTxLX32r+/N7/fXMOevfVH8iqOOPjv2lcCVgbdoHboBet/rWV0i1ydNWxagyQ2TiZQWfbz6SYjoVXL7G50UOUYkoVfcXUGbc4YqblCVKlmPzvxL7iVsrAaa/TmOsS2YTljDb7XmF7eSpPmKhe4O17+LoUCzm/+rwWDgn5qGEzvJG+bG8G+kn5l4Qn7764sv7kZdWEOE+jLD09hqAtnKNuXgDaiXNuHijG7O17xl9qi6JfUJQKjdKHMilfxMpFubutH9QxIvqB3NK6bmT0HBOTNH7I82EhtaQIJHykMX80/sFyji90syV6OvLYhcpPHTtSGcsPjJLALNaTeg7fq4MvpneuFHgVZu+bjRZfGkDhTfMkdMaDyH+7TX/TfX4jkS0OTkC/K63jYqjhE1M1r48SSgM4GmVkr82XN/bzHNQbOPTQEq3OJNSrdWSjo9GlscacvyDGMjXPEQsE5z8Bxrzrb6i7GJTZMEjKnCoqeKnZ269FhbA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8001","langCode":"vi","question":"Sx4Lt4mzV/uh6sD2La1cnwOHJKZDNFEl/YhBSmiaj9E\u003d","answers":["blows out","calls for","brings up","blows up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5EXuOHz2tPw7fl9WuLHZ8TzC3xo5rbVhcBZvS0CDBXMay5CKts9dilUZbZ+sck79Ax+ZaEZhT8f8limn6kjxnupJPXQvNfj+aTwPDCulW9UgN/MiL0WXUucDOm0f01PeHgLfE9dNwNNSHo3RZT9WvzK65qNh7LJcfc8FTk/HzAyErbSkVEdkaZZbWdNhrHXZLiX8gn7qZKIac0awryFGSe29egdALV9PWnQ+1Vjxu5aw901museR+JHOTQLd6vA0vjY+KwSEdcozdz8nM5sPl4crxODGr6QS8WDXeBLCQTD/1DiKgObtwyBApGRGxoqBSasO2UEZOFzqXT4X3Un7LDXtR4i+wTpN3OXdn6FGiTh/jBWIeAoSK/P5qxuaRpfPcXJtTNjeNE8oU48VkmcwIqE\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8002","langCode":"vi","question":"yFfZvBfJApwks4lPE2VxlqfGI9YVelW45jjS48AMlzLKj79ziDZgSgpHsmlCLfZZy6HUQeXUu0eOx5mSziqcbg\u003d\u003d","answers":["call on","come up","look for","call off"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"8zUOsyhpo8hUs1A1X8Le5KuZ9De0q/hu10Cwx2sTxLU8Knn3xtKxQiShmDlAiptaU69VGVzOpzrQPyrwNPZLwKcxYrZP9fJK75qXe8VcELESz57W5mW6Nk78Ys2rERHS8H2FeG5OW5Uul+AhF+8260SjJHax0iMjgd4fkVHOb+NxxWJbrPPqjknkuFH2tBGfKIAc88Nfol5N31cGlD2FTojlg9T1DJMDhpw1ujm9flCwH9niTWsj7ttN94X81lGEOPv6sWlJ6yglrgHHhKce7XYpsdeluBeVsalOP6ZG8I61b/UoDa7gqdgupNt/U0PF9sDhpZuBapXTpqQygozzPj3Ru5AA3quKHYA/hQyUAV0z0zOf83tz+VPIPq2rN2Gmz3YQOPNMK07UtW5YR5ymJg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8003","langCode":"vi","question":"OAXMkTjZR+gSEmHxq3WZ1PHF5mhUgAKjVTOiJqNgIU6mQBxSdJsJkFW3xY+VfOES","answers":["brought up","bring in","handed in","hold up"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRB+vI8bEFpH5cv5MkHue1x5urqQzKNYPBpEBgjFgeKnxF/CgFYCtUD/BuHdBGoSZ8mmLLu/6EVrU3mYJbdUfCfwWhCPXS3oUlo0DCr1HekUxa6OevsZ4wrV1TZ1qQr3wrr5OobXNZcOlBSNuVNFM6bY4W7zI03hpX7cScVS9n3NJDqs6PwETUm2lRwF531eq30J2gj3aw14QKu3PtV3dZAe8E8ay2vSC4arLiFbCtOZZFrsef9PPsMdbgjlRSopzITs9oE43ZY0B2Zj/gyDp2w8pkmU4yV4Ha65y3f0gy7lI8GQpAeiEj1V8OVh6Zv0SkEU3hbVoPWo3PSF7HHdNZ3rtFSgk9iFU4eR5VpuPkv2w5nHDaHMbVUX7s6iRSe3mp6OZACdmVlyHYbOXVo05C4LNJi4db1g2sjJGla4jTzH2aJ+PpJlvsoVTXGPfbikMeo\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8004","langCode":"vi","question":"T4XYSIbWYS6kl1hRmUDypzLue/5zx4vqEl8VjEZ4/Xs\u003d","answers":["hold on","give out","go on","grow up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRBRfjc35STxOz0w6IRjisrrcRSgsDJDt0+oOGXvU695KjcEje2hkpUmz8bBLPQkSuzslkcW8tC53wYHnUdDligDmU3jpUE3BrfuBJMMFfwHVWNqCYOHyqpzpHmptIfMfr7W0tScnEJQhSFiFHIeETJBrWSMPaF56YQBuL+R3PAMPN5N2sxbhxApUk7/9vLsGhDF/PueNGuYDi75M8GvhcXcKgCAgpJS5JFQsBsZ7lfe/m+d767yayMwgysy3GfBR0ZGum+1Rj8P1ArQ6J3YoufDFUsgP6hiPaoSp49MFZ34E5M+kQZVCLZFtvdnzAg0ehh3zLMPbXDJrrdY+zs0Mx6w"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8005","langCode":"vi","question":"xkbBTq7kf0ijFq323eOsYCRX6wiJ3oq0ujmbL5i/3fZd8/MfO+tPjggtbrxDnUfAZDeXjigcwhrbk403JFp7DA\u003d\u003d","answers":["got over","got on ","got up ","gave up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQVC2rIn83Ho9OgoOkYAI5m+MIiL5xP1ISkhF4XyiADcRaEA9YbsDy7T3BTPmDRP5Yj9SColJIldm7GWTyeLx0mmP3w+N3Qfi7ebaB503NQ6IZI3KtBOaoGvrxuLg45S5J5gDqlwtfKZ34B5sQTSgn6nfFMuyd6iBussLUtCAEokksWEV4Midna9IG58uWb2LvWkIhD0ZFvUqTB8hziwYSYQ+sNJkLToxTfeLdEZebHaesFBM1TF2Dmz8aUmtymQsfjk3pYriaPpXJ2Vy0KSimh7unhVRUVo0SRnJJLDT8/Pfax6OeJLj57sV70PkdjXqeQkriWxMGK/kSTACj/QGQEb8HBBOwcaUmo77pogC2zJUPNXj/BAFrmGjRLwPp8mT4vH/Dg9pEEmxX94gV5dqYEUqVRUIMvxTo/CrXEpuvNiW0zYfWmb8pZzJzr8bbKTBg1vpxP+lqy3gi0XvM8WWNDFbbv2HN4UZf7JqBUO/e9XL8Jkih5RYkoCR7pHfGUwWFl+CQvjE7Ikl9AqVTzPRkHpJAi8Myl94l8fdYwxl430w\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8006","langCode":"vi","question":"HryMv0/YFyRdS02K6ILfJWGYwfl8Ka7/xclLJoiT6sfV8KOUxPEi7Y7nIt6OGE4RnoJ4sE4szWtJ8G/46S0muqfy32oA69xhNyPGmDofVwVS5myLsCtyRklufvs/4YnQ","answers":["puts on","takes on","stands out","sets up"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQrJuZp3xNtBs10DIk9i8e+5F8fGtgiYtXu3ws1Iq7QBTEtR30rgqU/YbqgdE1RCOexc1epHZElGO18abo/NrYT2bI9eS99dBkYT95rv9uXOMKAFcJnR5INaOstRT/9HpG0FMsFroVKarjWw2AOQhAbKCrgpgLfkwLWL8tHmf+UAj36lkKR3bib25qhuVjYaYqqlG+5CJ+SOUJ7TI3VHVd0pt7tUHI3p4/Adymy76L3dL3FvbiCSGkn08E7kKAAkDe1tLUnJxCUIUhYhRyHhEyQSGSgYYOjdK8qP+PPphPeIuEkVseEePSnS6tbHNH1mnJs2hqo5vfB2OxkYQHW/E+Joh0VvVO7iVzs7BiT7MEeZXXzb9XOfxBZiCqKBW7FMGbhed7taWI8gYv0UtW6DGvNm7NvjuljEbUV3hftlsqOWKyIWSGYkIDkXOm6uPaZN0GHG5a5IIJWaoyKR4omiJLkU4cOpZ++xrdcjJCsDcxJLxUnfNKioLG42BXC8adOs71n3Ghg+koTwI4HgNmgCiXfg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8007","langCode":"vi","question":"4oTO8xT8Wqj1Q6FWmFxHmnXAVVhAPaGkRYpy9BQQgo2WFe5i9gbq7Mm04zlw7r15TJjH2wr8mYihLtWy7245LA\u003d\u003d","answers":["put forward","take care of","take after","put up with"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQnhg2hRXKHKUdLmA3H4o78NStprHqu8SdA1TDw48qKHD1mtZEHN4CyWpgPOMBdDmTn73Dj9BgykSolWIm10ULTBVpD+R20EcoLWjmOeYQ1nRWTkn/3yu9qFrufBYS2XuyA7dxXZOzUf+UK122LodhliSdoTAVh5DpzbN79IIXYTzAsmtbe7bt/UJ7Ywk+f7NCbiNTKWXTbBcjCJm6B34EqfR4vMQRJyQQS5TgpvqzAs44uXvOL8mMCl1BHsLfqmoyo94/m3jxd9zPm3WenKLqk23ZDCc71fBWdwY7GRcceuYco2J56r6wUO5tr5upFRbmKfSfqe1vg6CwL1Hlfr0L3KHbawmI7uwlELj63G7uFC9fFovDBMXU2mK5ELI4ajungZEYwv89voPy5cuJe3C/41QPTdVUgdokpDUeW9MhNXcPVlz914rd7hNcQFYvh+V07+DwnmhQv9bx8acj5qM9NX++rQIm0Vqa3F20VdIsIUM\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8008","langCode":"vi","question":"mcA66ru5tf/+aH/hiZgZ24p9YTKFJLmxahNScqIo3du/mGPQWML1MkRsWmEbRr00","answers":["takes off","talks over","takes on","gets off"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQXczZXFMMVUeIm58kQzw1dXKRbif27Br9ZMgXadGKjD/ZI75158Ea7vKNNLcFDrACwdz9x06nigKr+DSStizc3bIK+kzICRf0xdnZgQAkgKL5MJxi0DslN1V1+5kj5ZD/udN1Zdq+zaNlC+IvQNFPW1wdvEm7RUSGPRfI0doExGAl11WPB3puwmto8nABDxr5JTi5NvrG4v2TsAultZbC8qMsCKGUQxjngRy3KroLd5N595BZuHDHis3BXiRyzwdX9FuFZJnl29FOuklxoci7Q0h1wKSE3C+otaCz7ml6pCvtbrXTcyc4DUtrYca/qqKmVg9fvNhDEzm+vc7ZfY+TyIAFATI/k8BQwSghTohWBKKPzOh9BpXpN/kculXy1N2K0nioUz0YJy4cuSLdhTPh4A2pebjS/tjzDTOYQYDGsQU\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8009","langCode":"vi","question":"I3sW7wjtbWPv1oN/zOx1s2vcdD5fDrWIOy1iBoKN26Fjlxq3vykh25owdm5lZznqQ0tAoSR83Wx+9o2FItD/YjaUvZVpL2HKOq+k79XLgE2EbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["showing up ","taking over ","setting off ","running out "],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQJfVeTW+uZLNFN5hNXYTO3MVsgZip5kB+pk7BnSnVsqzjnRbNa5ihyi6Ed+yTzCy2IW2WEDHOqtV10lABI9jMYLP5zzNrC2iejZRsHv73arm9yvzGOmrIWOSWLEaz7ybZEnPW+hHNWWaX+zyeH/puJuYA6pcLXymd+AebEE0oJ+qkC6tAQtC4euUd78yiXsGa+yq2bLkPxaggPdMfcef18yMWxaNkcAlAqpK3D6syS+7w31AXhWe+/wpIkF0w2213CdoI92sNeECrtz7Vd3WQHvFHB8jUdH0y5h+1i7YDElBSmeIfwcl/gf+KtdCSSc8LOCOwiR4pfQtk748/RW3pb3hPl6SgqqBNcIO48rogJCgwRkmlLlaNsaXJbnUqrbCTCZ00ONM2L1VOdBLbQyUsgDJrCdzZYrNM4EHbjPMduC27H9kTD9k0NzLW1yjiaq5b"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8010","langCode":"vi","question":"JhVsdobIRHIRrYJFbQdJGNfI1awiTUJhC+OjEM9DCcc1oaA7wKHuZqSja8qn12wv","answers":["fix up ","set up","grow up ","shut up "],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQ0kGDCplqVsFCPbjmVZ4l2DMlJw8p9vcH2ChanX7P/evdaaAkgODsgdRU3gEHyc6cyz7siSjAngjwI+JpClo8QxPq/unmU9vgXx0qFy9oBgjVw/yy/3wBiHBTNvXwZG81cTYf/toopTCiFtwxzCqS5iHUv/nm+vKcu8JTQ0kIfw1XLhJ0OTWa4bJGwiVEnmVRse6fA8629TMXsxDgm1kWBg6bcxrHhnP+Rf0qNIMALJHgLnyEV+UIN3ebBi5NE8a6QDzqWWZORD0uR53fJHvMQTPBGdajfk7eH9dhjSojJ507P0kJZR6OuHgwg34pXN6NhmD0mtvg+9AtGqpveN8Jfcvy9OHtRn+jcoTrNHY2BziXl7AeH9MIPayAmyDBcVXICioH3HysB4YbnU1dRbIqP9wJwhNUQb0218Iwh7+svxg\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8011","langCode":"vi","question":"KOGccIfzilHCFK0a8V5aDzYTJ4coCbA+bC6PBViObf2Xzf0G3semlJMCi2Es4kS8gPKR87TdsUeUcb63rj649g\u003d\u003d","answers":["get by","cut down","go over","show off"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQ+NqAt8tgIWlzP1jLcuDHz19Akq77B1HAkbxGIiP8rRaznMRAI2qb3VAEKf3lx1dvTuSycWLhjMuuoNQ/7IFAO5SoFDvTK1A7skTmRtqgIJK3S38SXlF7lFCxGcnAvo3BE+r+6eZT2+BfHSoXL2gGCNXD/LL/fAGIcFM29fBkbzVxNh/+2iilMKIW3DHMKpLmeN4dwniHiWmzB11/N0+pkuoUMs2QBvGpwzc9hf3EXJN5ymtZd6ZoMkNuGjDm11Ysse6fA8629TMXsxDgm1kWBkipMWp09xpeb+f1UzQTu1yGzeiP2BrnJFWe7ifVEZFplGKc+5l3Da8kxeQmPClGgXiY5GFMDwJMPICJaeeqIV3ncvVeiiI0Ei6E62MKBjiM1Yjf5mLapWi77rqChi2QyHHY4JK/mrgzUi/VNuJ2TsEkRxWa5DqHbta22UVvVVmHDCdiJZhOMN2A1bWEtlTSLDkEQSK+yCFQOoYxFAT9NZkE9TotayjpPLhRr5UIRyUEU9/SRsNWDB1LqPwVgf7oGwexJ39fYGDmpi3FfeXtn/DxUr2vJjrr49SBvpE5VJZH"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8012","langCode":"vi","question":"8RJs8NwxSsDbZ3E8FYVXV+Xgn+HSQLCYztPFUJtV9xc4/zguPGIvOHDSLJWNqJ4Vp2HhoaXQHRH2retcHVsJVVbbmhqxSn6m1I9WGK0xSn4\u003d","answers":["keep up with","break into","get on well with","come up to"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQK/bMiyQ8+dEA+ICB5XBTZniQsXsLlvLPAAHLvg4ZMhVEFjGcjW2qafn7J9TQEtcVz1jVxNmXgkmOsqNgXV1ci80+tcNtUGjALKBLaIJszv8ymtFLAWZNzSjdJinGbbXmRX9MPnfVPbwWT6Isf1M2PwsxoCIBUBW2WmLI0/6faJZaaFEetSkXhshm7prVjwy4CyXuIxB+u8wTRnM/GA/jQ1VFSvXbwZVkij7o3Bn+bBZyFfjxvUFElVIJ75TC2uAO5XnAfsdqkm8ncrQd5so2/n0C5UVQJqI8VAoLMtLPL8DkUWqgysD/HevDmw/rKS8PmG8sk6ttoMvVG5m/k19XHdWHqujJF/EsGVNDh0IdSsKWfFw1w4tDyyDNrert7Feszt5ICGSSKftSnDZJ18J1O4rUwTiye2zqHE8PqkLQWZ1ThvHq4Md6rxKL2JZfOrMSD8HL8xPwH1Hdwy8rgGhBwII2N5Tfv28tTERayFYcjCgVvyhBjVgfW3viChPSuHpN"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8013","langCode":"vi","question":"a7idz+/Wg01SxNSJD/+YEyLDOrqyo0fygNwdMqjrpduWhhZHR+zywNsMPsqI8n2ectg7aLmI9JiPjVh/XCeXKQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["look back on","look for","look up to","look into"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQBvoy13cn6tYN3A1CwYy2lLXaiqZ3vVhPtINTIiU7Sj8ma5Zkn/TCfFoU6yeE6Zs1GJ+mY+OsOinL4fK8xFn3MeF4y+ftPQ43doukVBkdq0zXBcnvViqow+8UKdO/w7nppyx73dmR/S8IiQGWQ3lH48K4W2xX8+OEeeoNHtHRQX6vShXdq3VxSpEpRJO6/d+u57OwBU/KR3cXlNPzELRLfmBxyLLp9uywiX8U2nBIMRBxw5UmrclmlksgZhXTBlZkccViW6zz6o5J5LhR9rQRn2DiX9MN6gMxztMx03lLzljzk7BBmZzo+v4VFWk/+kLwASL0fDmvD2MhYpYFqPkKm/2JvlGosG09+aDF0Z7mdODkGgI+5NeduW5T0ew+4kFjuDm6a4ZmgdEXMvpPVYKdqZEt1bAvNMJbWP5aYxMmIZAsirLImGBcSs157rwZH/1U89M1E/15wqz9nDtLo4evrHep5uCGaMwL+IpEvH+efWfArrm0fpld/3AWBBHh/p/RRUA6mWlE2dw8BeCA2EG00w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8014","langCode":"vi","question":"bsK7Z3U9/ADuVD9g47CM8nKmViu4xlrjBHW3QMrr+KTmNiMO6us4rmUYsMgM5oCzRTDJVLBNw0m9Eag2YAGiGw\u003d\u003d","answers":["giving out","looking into","going away","going away"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQbvJiYioAu00xTMIycEWu6dUqRTE+Yu2QWKsA6tByyD+4/RaFSnidL2m6+fhD0fIVI3ilq0dF9vX+wF0O7qUSB7oZ/4UXYq/W6Bt8SPK4z+Iu162jZx87wkqgmyic/58T4NAdzTDJqJ9dA8i/LvrgOhDpiBDDOhYFXelHN1oZw7JXHYFHmWZoABUUOfOgb3CL00B3NjtVDrxbwrYkTSLDFKhTcV3BrVlEJ+gb7ddG1QceHWbnz2W2/g0963rM4PWJ2U7wfGZ/nnndDbDCYXgL7wXqCpR7mxfAJIYEvUfD5KM0FP1Mi+xuNgGn6EP3Rc28dzOr2Wa2CUKvb1Jjtt5l0W2cOcj2pNZSpHUEwicQVOC+eO2I6bjhxV9IecxOgxUkGpf8lar/wDirm5xTB/wgPOlab8DPqC11uqKrRtyMLpmoK6Z2BnbQNBRwAD+963QG"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8015","langCode":"vi","question":"r8pJ09aSeWo3S3HZ3n49doJcD8cqkoY9iA39gZZKPkwzl1PJMNEUSm0F655nBxNE","answers":["look out","break down","call for","bring up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQX3pMkbTPkJJ1SPZvznUtHkA0U5Goyp4fx+b0CKKW2kWpFxc3nCbtqDC8ZfHUydjrt+BUoeuaH86fD+gWx7D3Y/9zCMW6Ikcf3CK1Tl6N667nWRCpRouS3z8Ap3d8iNCnPVqjU1NkwXzEEiDY7BFLeNi4uBEofcQI6L7S0tij0aQXLQ767QQIqgAIa7bu0XI69RHXmcZnD9Dj6YbxMvtgt2wMtRVJNobuwpLKrN1xyvLJlUOX3x1Rt/xMcVeeg7Oylv3wU1ucwljctEdG4sYgQl7UA1UgM+3BnWVVZ8xU743709fqN3y2/kiQDOOysuw3t7nWwPOLAKKg1yfH9bI2KoDGIOPk5aTFUiaietvozbYF4DKjFYDxOoV97yuQ9AfghG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8016","langCode":"vi","question":"0tHxZcEL1IIo2s27adzvG5Sh8TWuNs/lBVBSiHIuUjuTTa4zYXipnwxxZdDcwqLIURVp6+IzvzpGeOwhNdycwJLVJP9O8dnBGHgKyE3v8Mc\u003d","answers":["turned into","came about","turned down","bear out"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQfMk4kwhJjS0jYljydmGHJSlfgLzonagLua/IluNeP1tZuIwhzAZkq/23sH91nFR5KsbvqV4464mEoH7MkMY8hGrbaI+wVR3m/XGdojOwYtCkyYaFeO+BztQ29ZNKGFCkzILcfSs1JOmvtdd/uP2+H+YA6pcLXymd+AebEE0oJ+qkC6tAQtC4euUd78yiXsGahJNOpDnER1Pa5KNAjGNCGj/JqwL4iLYV4UGy7fVEqGvvu+9zQNf6vxLI9dwQHin89vWTbmyVi3BFGYZTraUIq65/qg5HWfDsyhlRJOp9gvYftivR7a0Ui3GeO7u70ihlmLHQXFjn+002A1llWoG0BYVFhMTptjQ/KL/8UN2pco0dZA+Vel4O0FICUpminzKPazwnXD8buztoInw36EZd/dF3eu8HaQr2slG341oIWnuJftv25sGjn8Z9NNi5bWO8nXbE4rpG5kvK+bH5i2YFxVODRHqrqOV97Af0quwVXHwLqSx0jWGiB8tvR9LvTw8+23MgJx/FLekF0Jfsz6AZhDbmrQO/cEj4y/W1kHJwtjc\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8017","langCode":"vi","question":"TF2lXxlj+Emuf8Nb5zJTe7cunbAQB5h60TXNu/LdnbEEemT1oUh68MQ3fkQefmrbP2mF6zL430PIp5xqTbOfGw\u003d\u003d","answers":["carry out","go in for","clear up","catch up with"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQ0nseeIC3U0IP3ndB8sOalWfGhj2ZoDhoa7kimwThWsNh24kJeifkbwEbCv4nA26cSymwyN0wbABcBS1mf5OIefLGqYN8h23YYBEMTxd7lfDmAOqXC18pnfgHmxBNKCfqpAurQELQuHrlHe/Mol7BmihmD/uPMabVOEal+vcsDkeCRe6wZgEaa3WvvYpU8nO4ccOVJq3JZpZLIGYV0wZWZHHFYlus8+qOSeS4Ufa0EZ/4rbcVminz5w2al/bU9BRn0rleklSb9qcmOA59vIEK3mWuCeDOpaA0aaEPlqbVld9wPsYjDQ9x3+DOQ7YL+fHcYX7cpMp86twMJPfzFafheLQgBbYDBGinK4nYKZ6dwTPoptSxZtmoTy+jgVni9z0+11Urwia+UCXTB86B6EoUoDu/NkJO9T0DW9wJkKUXz9dfNvuBU/tHSBfGutBiUIBZ4CFMCFgdxwEOtARcBimyzgZCEf075jsG6R2bLY6crbo\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8018","langCode":"vi","question":"PeX6GYiz1V88ROd9Q3v17/NqSlsAvyI+0j+TwriPsHtWY739S9HqLDCs4u7dYlt7yitX/YTR/s9brQNSygJFeA\u003d\u003d","answers":["get down","do away with","count on","look down on"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQLbJJFF68+z6dDDnkg3JSMaRpluwatSXkAhIS7yP/MGK+zvpbBHbkHq+dGCxjnIFCy/PIYFRL6bdZk/Na6H8IEWf9lfQ4Gs0/+1xU27zYDtMhFqWMdDyLI5Oi/oYKK3WpBPJe1MG7SE+Crs67daIy/vL9BYOBClm0445D/4XYlhl8E8KriQ4WUNOGcfQVTBSgzYwZG8SoAtobSRMIfdvjOa5/qg5HWfDsyhlRJOp9gvZuHCRiB/8EvZSK1h0EgFIcviZcqjA1mb/hgZ96/dGAxv/o9f9Vloh+DE48dzjydXe/niWhzzCHRJIRIsj9oIK9NSgCQ8MB9RSW+cjvIwNfxSEW7OwMUH6Mw4xeuM1pTsWUBqsIWjgMeGKk7OZeiTxfVK07Dvg6bQarpBGtQrFjK3gy1V37wrxxLpmyUJxMBo4Gb3LaIVpbv5lNBCz4NeBE"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8019","langCode":"vi","question":"sx/nmCgyg5SwjCoyPhB4Zgl60z0ctlxKbo1oNNzU0QbXpjGZiMIKDFY/o/RzMIXjhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["call on","fill in","call off","come up"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQ9CW+V6ZUIQSZpcThpMLZ6SmTbTyFu1DsPAopvcnhxyrqPnRezp7NVLCh9lx4flCtxzpYGrBAZX+UJQvWdYSSCwxcC3UIvu70CT3Z70uiAeDzYnCr+9qMcpV2kWJqHpc9fJs6XbM8LE7qkMUiINxYChPpaQ+39FY/N4OLNClssFh7PfyYfBhE81mXYVjQ51EkRiiUl1ZBzN8bWr6KqI/0e65/qg5HWfDsyhlRJOp9gvY/33mYTx77Ae+6N/2y8lCWqfkWrNkmyHYaSim5ugepS48TF6RFa3nQmjZISREaXCAtFDDEKmYXUzhUePqopSC9vapg3RpAyWPoczj5j+CXZykSFhv/IYx/9+RdkFVQexLRpOeDHb+QzJDX34mjyWGKuvP4bHJ4vnz8SQxeXdMuKw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8020","langCode":"vi","question":"+AoD28fZmPljy2tokaGqWxXpQOmKeRSbRPUJ6s0T08w\u003d","answers":["left out","let down","made up","burned down"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQg/fdcca3G/7BYbNw1Cgm3bilZklH2Wd1n/6sPEOsWDIRHWTFT+w11KCABbRPiziN82Jwq/vajHKVdpFiah6XPXybOl2zPCxO6pDFIiDcWApzm7wpdytMHRYAeeUgMB9ggnMEkyZ1WHZSkSO6hJERmM64UgqdR3syUKsVa+00llCx7p8Dzrb1MxezEOCbWRYGW8NDZ0BA+e6WNW96xdl6YrbKnLvfpH8PsOCKRJFwBt5vibRr+Tp2TnxIlD1NlYqOeSDAbd5zdaZ7edONw3y6pqdDoOjjX2jDipDwwOWHSeoBXrt6SVWEu/MMBhROcf+rK3hi6XDQ7r75nkx7RvS5Kv8V2/MPvuL2pJcc8MXCWTxmBKUQZ+RaoGHIfqwmGl2Hnpt+wSUKWhpdohtH+naZ0Sr3G6XQzzoUPreywVnp2U1f3Bga59THlRrp2hLPwy2WEUiQsdWxJTJEZtXBiDL7qg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8021","langCode":"vi","question":"GGXKYP1s1EeKgNiS6qsvzGs+hJEDKdRwnOgYsYnSDOQ46o0mDyezQgLpI+P31UvHhNJRVLqeCs4v+xMUORD+L4OBUUh2JEYuu06tcR88n0c\u003d","answers":["pick up","burst out","sent out","put up"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQ+Tr1GtDRKm1AI9SUvw7EUHECUtYybBirjjVSu6vLhQy6Sx/fo/6/L4j9cyevraiOgxWJugOGnwxH9Sc2g14yAR2FiDclLhgoj6AKSKPsfqcRuXkdV8SwduncWD3i3sjeBFt0h5WbT4qstk8O1ZPctsxFF5Oo30sHFKKx3REDPBC0K1XipKiiusK2LrsAP60FXM1tHFlsFTdw4c3TaA4bvHrn1LpG0cV4hePdWQP0/OcI+Z90Abr8l7/21Y0/vn20rn+qDkdZ8OzKGVEk6n2C9tE3gD3+6YIB0v+pGP4G7N9GDL098RX8dFlXhidt4/vDe6h+5doUCe13iTqI+uCSvkz5ndzeG+3/AZbGTameqPle7syDkeByr7de51rgj+AYM1H9EBqezuW+rn4xCFp2jqKImf+xMyk6C1H6t5r48zVnfhdqVNJAZ9NPL0mYz5Krt9a/MkNFXa602Pix1396K938OdmCULRdnI3A9ivemaALVXyVHCYY2m3B8ImSWTNYQY0Z0hNWvVifOepFGMGKCw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8022","langCode":"vi","question":"xP24iLjI8NORnDLgnvfYjxd7WdKYZD2TZttsbeUEW7e6duKOZmD1b2UgIK3rwJktViG5OCnNx9ZbYUg7ANhMSg\u003d\u003d","answers":["broke out","called off","went over","broke into"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQdznj+91m0G5G+zXljDovXH02VSyYxbeiP/HXELvzSBR6aceuPUeJGQ+HGCqHULDFnZKnzg+Y4PuxzcBdCvG3thgY1fC3efSRrDuPYfDOxGDumaQx1XaM7xqdKlT+ymeJE+r+6eZT2+BfHSoXL2gGCNXD/LL/fAGIcFM29fBkbzVxNh/+2iilMKIW3DHMKpLm4FFGIrCv5ZNr1upEKk+wWMJixOnOz/NCTGRQn577kZp+xE1X2AW+EwVGEMxhbT1MbnNy+G7W6XCOHFjDCVKCV8kKryvt7fS+31dJ2UXTatx3tduzaU1gBlvsoJcJtLWpFnom+lGhzMvEEN0lnmpIo5FEktKmQ3Hyx7DB78Jb4JaDa3+hVbyQjd7TDbjAfytbXh6iW7Ya2K/wra+muk9jcFP36fIJldSZpv02IOWrEailuJzGNqjf1YL2LCUFWjuA6lqXxuur7I1HU15cukDcSDXMbtXxP7pIwu9vPDb5IqA\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8023","langCode":"vi","question":"LRQS6dYdpfbmMcjmsxvhrun+9tqubbors2yXJ6YgO4C3tB/2X7vUL0tWaCbN+3iehG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["hold on","look up to","call on","take after"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQGrIPuH0rGvsEAQ5pLMNqVSk2KVja05VbnvNfupqUVUuq8RVYyHVxKnjsh9h8pURerzjfKgYarTI5j8oMewcSe+yuzWBORRDSKJ4xMgeKjcs8HWir3zUmJ2PopmBXMLQhzEUXk6jfSwcUorHdEQM8ELQrVeKkqKK6wrYuuwA/rQXtWfW5tUbD9tRq32CvlIayfWIThBj3jGnD4kBrr/17NFN3hT/eCVXZBHMDKJLSluCr1M2qmbZKA0I9Gr/OmoBy2Li4ESh9xAjovtLS2KPRpBctDvrtBAiqAAhrtu7Rcjo+XDvXxflCE0D5kR4h5tZi4Uae7yzgaoQedD/UHF6N0r9X1c/DmlTv4TJeigy++/XwLpYaos4F0+MjWMvcP94ScTltIT00JqeRMjwqWA0JFmUeQ4lRefllkfs7YhoCRUurcATFCUBmtVBXysUPFvmCETF06MqXDG7zZAiTRnPRj4VsKeL5jeWIpwzEI3qKbIIm3NefBClp5XHTkcTYZgKX"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8024","langCode":"vi","question":"ytr/uBHWNQieAxZpzLaidgu3+kSPxSpIYiJSMynXQ55K3r4txlieYJYeoTh9Qnj459MDd2JpHjHLCxxLQj9lLKX0M4XzTS0YAU0Jqqw/ieE\u003d","answers":["run out of","cut off","turned on","went away"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQyczxLevrQmUIv+14/oPzajty2/sIrjhRSnuvFFH7bfNktuk7WxvM6cvWWvpT50ZiGv9Enpd0HLsweb7/T0Lq4oa/PqIGazD3chqZ/5Qp/776oyojdJ+AmfPFUm4l5Ag5JJ2hMBWHkOnNs3v0ghdhPMCya1t7tu39QntjCT5/s0J1sxCyl6s/5Jm75BwYllrx9Ir/Le62rlimW12gfXO0JQ5M1xWwXDdEPvkGgSZmefeuf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL2iW3f7UZjehGJj5bKC9rb8/cLfTo1OnnKhnVmFSnmjyvy31LVMM6s2yL5bQk6ICfs+5ThXuTseSHFUAsZL/wOyKDJuneuIQLGDtjZS5PG4/akKaTftzSWuNcvoCLAY5r2S7UxpfBDNfztOXEBXJfe5/nnb4+ooFEi/BaTUQsav3E7oV9giQrvAwNw+dApamw2cPyDpWFUE+7PSQAP4ppBXxR21ncoGRiew7hqWuAOumHOeJFhbMpZJMv6rAxO/1UQwIb98aAMkaLtD6s4DwkdU6a7Xn9hdsc0SWdDfCDsyCxmEqthzo0LY9rt1qRF2cQs+zq+Bq4KqZ9yD8asi8AKya+Pswoi7Lovw2ZEyMVxyN0\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8025","langCode":"vi","question":"/Uu9OnYy7w9OzB22epojowKKN0wZQwBEwryElu/s7dppwpa80eMqMpwmK1q48uVx","answers":["cut down on","take part in","catch up with","fed up with"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQrJuZp3xNtBs10DIk9i8e++norgoIvduXDI4hhd9PoH2jgZbt/kihS7klUiw74TYYmbHVxJwqd7l5qrfHsRAtmlBL7Qik5IOW0HaZiByGzI8knaEwFYeQ6c2ze/SCF2E8wLJrW3u27f1Ce2MJPn+zQihSeACETyC4HE/A5bPDdz4+EBcPbAgGBM3VUZTYA8R0zfiuA7scgykCS/ek7yWRe+V5wH7HapJvJ3K0HebKNv59AuVFUCaiPFQKCzLSzy/AyMmueY05mobhH+EJx6zShas0RZ8skX2O/I7FdyJOtG0JR2P4stm0icShjKQcgMnISuwIMhuexfglkAttV1GfRxoGor2I0lKlsRGcvb+Eb0BSFBUuiyL8U6O0kJM0dO4B6cPX2bN+j9hxwtnvY5qEDwH832lRFj34+OYXZrUfKk6r+sh3n0RD5ZYLK5IiHwov"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8026","langCode":"vi","question":"IBSsF3xKmdNWN4p2S2+VhGguWIWV1OsJx0C/y5W2OFhTFMkb0u97Ok9OlgcaUJuSo24kCzsz1FMeHxtzl1Zodw\u003d\u003d","answers":["dying out","calling off","carrying out","dropping in"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQi1sKGKOD1iTRxu0ZV4ZE4VYqr9Lt3IS8Gpi4Ajgm4RkBJyNUzeU/LHcjGOfuA0kiyVvL3rV/I8JtgrFRf8bBPeDQHc0wyaifXQPIvy764DoQ6YgQwzoWBV3pRzdaGcOyVx2BR5lmaAAVFDnzoG9wi/9rYorSYBiDVGFNY1u9K2WTwUsYNWf1qRh4U3K92Qb535yiLAiW/JX17LRvJLy7VVwdvEm7RUSGPRfI0doExGAl11WPB3puwmto8nABDxr5z6ZC7o8LmGjHImlVOi+2iWBcAwS326tJDlObPvqBHEGabfF2s8BY54D5dvcx2QnIqSl4Yf+qiXeruhEX90GE+PW9UNPC7LbdDKwTQNUw6qKC5JNfRjgcHvqB9DSd+kZfqhH2C5bywoAS2CiHNAWGxodQd7+MM1ewewE0GjL7PmjxGGg5sqQbxa8/VsRIzZ/mPiCTirlgfnODkjZKDGoOaA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8027","langCode":"vi","question":"3JC/lEFhtSuuf6Zg6TuyPkSDe6UGMtHYu/9B/YPJCbHb6DhgHEefHCkRUE8thF4Zu/GSiJodMHc8wTh16Y4mbg\u003d\u003d","answers":["get down","get by","get up","get over"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQrJuZp3xNtBs10DIk9i8e+y4hpLIkfu7xrt6LouHZl4gedEne7X9r38j0WamNYtVTjTum/Mbh7h4H5507mcZbHicfYd/pSKgup7VRYRT1E5ll2aj4QO3SUD/RsAtlshOn1wXJ71YqqMPvFCnTv8O56acse93Zkf0vCIkBlkN5R+OLk9XCx99vwhEL0eQnAHFqx9mhsRda3eKW4+6qYTW4ykoFZAwAaqHgvo9c2YafiH6BDW5pUlmSS7X22L5S0oJqsbgAlTP5NTBmIv0FL2rLnQNi3KUzrLa0YU8V9S7BjBwi3mAyHy9LEH1LHH722IbS5GeYzOOSmJ9SYNu/S7xVx/jPyVyR4i+Ei3N1Zql/dKNAl34V0Yq1c3czo6Q0wA5xdVhomyj0PD5ZMsJVNm4lb2WL0Bom39IUpsO9YvRUa3I3H3BaVqgeaO3y7i6K7XoyIPlGJvEIqPADz/+U/jzqTkYReUSD9efLLYbM31mnyHg\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8028","langCode":"vi","question":"O+TQdmCGdUrZZ6TRf1htVDJaP4v+H3oQBtWs6m5R7rMiH2Mh3sXCSw4mYoHKXny2dp5ygNQSiOHskzBT6iHSmRUCDMJDB4T68lOynILUF6CRP2x5FJ2/p4kwQnKx2Zxe","answers":["cheer/up","calm/down","get/down","find/out"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQe9QDP11F+3wNWuNxeQ+FTCyO7Lgx1N8yeatbSXLmDNDQxjsXiwVfHFTaiy+bDy+M7BNU+FxBMYfd7Q4UN2Xv6tqPYYc+fuD1EFvYKpBYY1PDX5m4sOb2h0p+wRFSKQyEL/q5KQyMdPt4M7pq76AG3yDOv7Pb0eW+Rx1eSNp208whFqWMdDyLI5Oi/oYKK3WpBPJe1MG7SE+Crs67daIy/qiCo+28rkg4plorv4bgT/4mz7saoX/lvUKOvtk4BBiMR1sUPwCBskhVOROUlVAQlwL4jxwcA91Yr/l+xUQ7kWGHHp44/7b+XP4L4q/r5BlEAzrJNXdNyFuJQIgyTTHvvuvx5PfmdTacR562G04i1JwbcFOBWVCvU5cAhpxgX5X+GGqivDCK8S2uxZwAQaSkV29tFDxuHPaDy6XJc6CZHDpaAGq1EFEKuq2gbHPZRGgDLu8hCeNWxB5AHpE5n7CTCQBrAN48hAYoN0AKeDxpq3E\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8029","langCode":"vi","question":"2MV5QGX5HPC10hmxobWnpK2PTJDk/KZj0jQmeDXRI38UaTifaxAWl17VyITTizjs","answers":["died out","woken up","fixed up","looked on"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQzl/vE54oySoaxcBZ3B9TzDV3mbCDgd/ruKUG+s8BsUyjxC9TFURQaGomizQsfM8RmgZFfZB6EJUAkP5H2hhSdX96nXxpYnIb0vvz7utcxhqpmvG6XK8FfE2+2Ore4cuY1bStBM0ogzHRP0sncsNfFQlIXlqQOU9ycYeweoiWgHaze3pdW4RqqMNDBegXY3FWAviPHBwD3Viv+X7FRDuRYYcenjj/tv5c/gvir+vkGUSiXle6bDMB9OlyggmCQDEc5GxfUQP81xC+fRHhRKTIVJ1F5MuaFIPqizs7dw1eJPRiGrWr9aESEesScLLNYWnfScN4AZk17Ka0A02xksxd4rGgMQZyGhvTjBx7ZLIKei9kAkYcDYtMLxG28Jl1iJe4hNiMzRAi6kdnDOFUhQSryALYwxLcXvdrRiNDuBqi+ApFQDqZaUTZ3DwF4IDYQbTT"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8030","langCode":"vi","question":"Ohcbz09rxYo3QfHoZc8apKZaaoIp5jI5WVsgtNxzJzZEO20RwOjeIQtzj7oi4V74KzP2K4qm7LslvC1xlgSMSw\u003d\u003d","answers":["speeded up","accounted for","went off","warmed up"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQsYO6oSSp46QXcvsJ5tT+NSSJPga66Up2JmAYY8a+ZZEqrywCQA469D6QZT1btHTbfWCIsy4ZzIgPaaltd5wE/WqSc6bPSonZExa2U0MWIOoxA0i1p5wbxluiGSAjWQbtTW7NIRrWJX001eIgSIArH+A/5RKWvCtm+rMntXEJYawU6RQmpHwTsTQp7ikhIOrUse6fA8629TMXsxDgm1kWBrVf84tKNEoq3xeMfg80Onrf/Pc+P2YVuoU1AYUdVQIbR7hSVJDuBG/OWtS58BCRv24lDj8DKVmtcegGjEnLw77qb77paKjxQQLoCibI/OukKZTdLLyNOsBRi4JgilfcaEIsWagfwiXVZBWg2qBCmbDvAyNwHyH2wjJeNa2ALrhxPBtnVX4rt/4LtFMqpgSJQ0DTIx5g9cY9OsXLjxXwfUA\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8031","langCode":"vi","question":"MDP+5LrRr2GRztuQi8IkhMRZWVjOKAg3OkmQiIPhd3rJvnTydbXUSL8Lp7j6MqCm","answers":["back up","come up with","break in","cut down"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQb7U9nAFTMNxySGZ4TtXNY1EJLnjDFcehn7Ty+JQut7kP89e38uniTvehvy/WKCdB82Jwq/vajHKVdpFiah6XPXybOl2zPCxO6pDFIiDcWAq/4Ri66sY3YFTQpsMMOjTHrMBlT4bdzhRVfELtuM1/Llj9/CaMD6bcknzhyUTDABquf6oOR1nw7MoZUSTqfYL2VuzcYgI0ZfzOaaXA3lOzSxTFW/MRONWblZloVNbmciXFTNPDPaoO1jGOA+IRDTSzZScLKx5jG4WhWsYhlkLYz5CAkBULRrlDsTBleWETw7BoCAwyhnolUv497iyEB7F4462c1g5B3lWoY1S/Gihx/LVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8032","langCode":"vi","question":"koTE/Vioxn4G1iIanEX7ZZ/zOped8qxSapDIgRW+EWoy64NnH55MTI8aTd1KcvM7KRS7Gc/eeX0yPlLpHn0BcqltQFmrY04HCDEVkYSR1kc\u003d","answers":["look back on","fill in","hold on","bring up"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQNMXznkNWz1ljufTbbB+xCazh6cY6KalAWLAmBblNoo8LvJc9uoS3XWWv2qRkxWauu6/Hvb6qJMAxUBOA8/8MGObzmPHVm7h5Qu9N0192NkGgq4KYC35MC1i/LR5n/lAI9+pZCkd24m9uaoblY2GmKn2LyozBstuAjhzE8Trs2qbUZVwNiRij4OjabZK5NP/1B5/Zq1dHW8LO0wXQi94kvzi5e84vyYwKXUEewt+qajKj3j+bePF33M+bdZ6couqTYb8aAZVpgurc4Hcu3LUm4sxV25OEuMUf5B3Qp2/gAsFcoJeUppJQU5dSr1aIsVuJpfiFhSZKe8jU0yMVXx0urP3CT0gmAXJjVQ1RVSBRYArje3uLNSaXFmc5gUx9To5sLGh7Rh6R11Z301QKyR27FA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8033","langCode":"vi","question":"QmcP1fK15Vna7ug1NBz0xB4C98XiwFdNXo9kQ2QlHSeC0aRS57Q7GOZSLm/zIcYu","answers":["blew up","got on","called on","went out"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQS/5curxg8oH1PXB6BydaZ5tJgCiJRnNWn4GQ7epZKNj4uM/KnptOhACFoPeWout6wdz9x06nigKr+DSStizc3bIK+kzICRf0xdnZgQAkgKJ+S2rPsUaS3QtV2XCKW0TZ4kHXqur27gNWl4byZgTQ2Ti5e84vyYwKXUEewt+qajKj3j+bePF33M+bdZ6couqTGHT2OYu80p+FXyWOEYqm5aZXF6BRXHVqrzg7xvuXRKNDP1q7DLH6jjeLg95eNiUw4bAmMKtiTBA6P2cr3tsaNUk/t5fsCKz+2OWqWdzZzat1qxIx3moltUcVxFMJg1vxFGKbwFPuM0AOO8HAFfZ8rolkw8HYVskBk++uX+S9XgInLdBc5Ri5ycGcp3yio8Mq"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8034","langCode":"vi","question":"4aBpZIF1DsoRahqw1vZGQ7U6hab8aVhqXSdnXkEP0IRMLEPnubIA4hmUjgOxlW2KhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["call up","break down","come about","turn down"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQjORT2w8PiXdcQVMLnWMuBAyiT5rQXJFLSDpiFimIGMXjoJ1RXLWp5R24o+mZ3wSHBX3nsQM5KE63uHB/JUTlB6HLLS/jVOAiNp2XwyX/JPwLMaAiAVAVtlpiyNP+n2iWWmhRHrUpF4bIZu6a1Y8MuAsl7iMQfrvME0ZzPxgP40O3OYcS5/KaqIeSd2UZptjALAtsLVPja0fT+D+VEN9NUnHDlSatyWaWSyBmFdMGVmRxxWJbrPPqjknkuFH2tBGf/806EQ3u1rSVV0xAXIrbFWErdakDDvrzpSzPTD8tXP3Z76Dv/u4J8pOZUTDY5BCsM+pV4EHUGJBw2F1N1dMNZJVTiEPuKeVko25c/ISgR6OtXWyC7K6dpYJOvHq/+bjRVOpUTM9EK/UssxH9qlxsUoT3lI+tE5Z/x3/jBv1v7o+H3WdXjFeL99CA4WXxQvB3"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8035","langCode":"vi","question":"YbYf79MvCGEcUrytZLPsfc1pbseSTC92gVAt8EqXHu69c2oirYoplhFHCTPm17UdLfapOsmVthd6BxALbebzvg\u003d\u003d","answers":["dropped by","carried out","fell down","thought over"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQUAXwbnTO6lFgX6kJxrMu7pTsZKN3x+s0KCA4GIoTM+r+83jwPr/5ZR1kd+b9AS4w2AYzauL2Imk9Rb4QAjm6Y0GWl75WsoIzbD7Sk7DOek5pYI3JyuXy2U8Cb4ANYfB9JQetAahEwlyLvx6Ia6Db+xDpiBDDOhYFXelHN1oZw7JXHYFHmWZoABUUOfOgb3CLM2jH50bNHwbwbWjCkb8ZLQd1uXuO140VpnrHEW8hvglwtokD6eGYLiWHnjmBuk7NAviPHBwD3Viv+X7FRDuRYYcenjj/tv5c/gvir+vkGURz32fxCwg4cJQVXoK+kgpOyGaerlTTY+90sV/q6GNSDdqKjwJTH8Xooqq8vzQWXEzRUVwuBPtR5Jju08nh3tViHifYa/PFFRROTBWOYotDklxNU6rZuLB9NVDbl/YiM6fpxIo1THeqpzilANf3MjGjirF+RF1fxtPwYWi3ADU8b6UJOdOr00cFOeMRrUWbrtk\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8036","langCode":"vi","question":"dYTylbcsoXxCAeE9eLS2iVzu98ulz8ma97AkDUICSE49TeLT7WbN7mTaaDapeiW5EkIbYyreeeq8HPGz3MFaag\u003d\u003d","answers":["came up again","caught up with","delighted in","put up with"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQ6bTii9Ms+0IfmACxY7xg2ECK9iVJzZfwCz7jIFLc6mHABk07aRd1yd4f/6ouoE6IFt978YbAsa3+ii8kLuJyEPPJq/GfUhpo+keNInIXFNK+5SG/Fk4RqDggdrUXKyw9MQNItaecG8ZbohkgI1kG7U1uzSEa1iV9NNXiIEiAKx/oU1NWOp7WyICPIfk53aNJQ7YJbrgg4mEuGUFBB72IFalCC90BaA6pxoANpZkkmeQ3Lvc+cvQk7MVzgdyEOwO3rn+qDkdZ8OzKGVEk6n2C9rvJiOb7yXPiurAwQ0Vd9mGJdkTLTlAA8IkepdFjZLvSyvi3eTsisky6Lrm/H8khbtFix5ZHD7Tsou7HHQ5/U5zvF9Wfxqrvu++P7IL64MLynCKTRjFL5keJdygTY1oGnTEZCgEK2AQmlzzq6D/N9rHGJLo2J45o2nWTWo7D2fhXF6pCaggdUMasdHSMCW++pw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8037","langCode":"vi","question":"E2siED9q/opwOAEJ5qw19tjj+MnRqVJ4RwbkUVh+xhpfNqWNdMMnSscIhpaR2A7E","answers":["running out of","looking forward to","putting up","clearing up"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQJC+YIXjIksB4oU+cxY6PUKa2DdpqoTXspivKzBTcrSmYN5N64CcFEtt6BTmQCmDntuWHLxIkIl7qL/oiDtdsXujbWXj5KKZtovIG0ZGt1v4QhpZB5dxc/m0qFwc/PU3x1/tBxxZ/MVZc2E+zyKd/iy5doJltK5uee180yv/CUZO+aQG/HxDvCHj3oGW1ZxbJccOVJq3JZpZLIGYV0wZWZHHFYlus8+qOSeS4Ufa0EZ90Avseh1nU9Nm3SRryBQgJSTYdRK0042qJgvHgikNgPgZzI+K6gzvCeL5vyUxxIDfGaEshFeEpGctG4unZdCSBjzpUirgpqOVSaCDsV/gybzatp2EsZ91bh+YRAwTvYsnxhIbClFcwX4nKwM5BdHrgdQpOcFSBXR8Cz8M8i1k7yUlwZ4L8y9BjV7VgCYBrqL0\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8038","langCode":"vi","question":"rWYnU7XRfHiOygU4UTfAvp8J0AJH5f7q7pwfEoJ8yJxFd7SeZZKNKm9+um3CNOna0xybrAsCyisLp+7zrSJavw7ilQ/yRMD/8ZCVLkoOvrmEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh","answers":["come apart","covered up","left out","given back"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQGAVcaBvUJZFCI1td5jxAIz3GYR+UwsjS9CjZ3SYjyKUCpRjC8mAjp2azgFNrdWoS0s46YQs1TydgA04+w9GZz9PKOjEhPRHhoWk1Nue8cjz37RkimQQOpNVA7mNwWxcmiOvUJDMYZmLcJ6YyOE44x1OShmYJ/AhQQ9mNkK5ypu2pmvG6XK8FfE2+2Ore4cuY1bStBM0ogzHRP0sncsNfFfTmiHrUI8kP5Qgnw4hhSkR08rNRTXkVYTFUw+Z6ZZ1EIq0euyvbPoTuDinmFrSG0IENbmlSWZJLtfbYvlLSgmqxuACVM/k1MGYi/QUvasud46V4oE0tDHLa5BQHd0F+U2wmy4aTQXneP0jBVfg8u9gHz12l8HdSSmr9yiXcxh78+p9ygI/Qd4U+azGddkTNexGryZJUHE3diZ8rJtPcvv+wlfR9SmR+A3y3O/j2gGKISGtjgx0P7DjPuvm8COHge+yZiAd6U2rVtrtnSmD3ZUmPNQdLRNu4QItKe/9w92F2RUA6mWlE2dw8BeCA2EG00w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8039","langCode":"vi","question":"Nc6C+eKmA+EG1ro0vmfV9/buH55KvT3NZxcRXQWsQoQ\u003d","answers":["face off","throw away","come up with","dream up"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQ8ATtDI1r7sDe9RTV2ez3WlRRKdy06d5LeWRgU0VsstlQnAWv1TFv/uRmztqam5EL1wXJ71YqqMPvFCnTv8O56acse93Zkf0vCIkBlkN5R+PtDdOa7kk3in/LYFqqZF4c6QFsFjGP+6Th+N5QGJYtkMOI7wNnmY6niIKFBgSBkAM4uXvOL8mMCl1BHsLfqmoyo94/m3jxd9zPm3WenKLqk8nYAP+5mv0yX1b1TivvRJsdTIfFdPs7yY0f7osbnoXnufabb1Ez5gYdVr3JIzmOKuFQsCg2gDT23U0ueYhhNv5VZbBdRMhGN3OlCnWhUB/l4PZAJG49gkqEe0v3x1bh5DJ/Rk8vTENsevV7oIlLfQjk10RS0sukyrBDxP+WW0r0WgEWUo6aWd+N5mT4R9Z1g92Qv4hI9vtZaNUyqSyHsN9FQDqZaUTZ3DwF4IDYQbTT"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8040","langCode":"vi","question":"KNwnopUHab8J1XKpc4owYB2NSG2WYvWtEeCTjrdp/bQYejVB/4Lzd5w7jzHzZwPjCs0zOI2zb8L13Hf754T7ZA\u003d\u003d","answers":["look up to","work out","join in","help out"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQX/YUnTFv9QczXZvSxfvKcO/31u/d0cyM/DSBmhAjoLv8qDq6uRQ8HFRXOeIJ8CcqL+JVcqVq/yW8ucqyZwHw3Pky3hEgY4kiVnuM+RqR+cQxA0i1p5wbxluiGSAjWQbtTW7NIRrWJX001eIgSIArH584PfdqNdLx4POw0rh8Dud/zxpMh7nuRJiYUDDQAayB5XnAfsdqkm8ncrQd5so2/n0C5UVQJqI8VAoLMtLPL8AYi60l7UZLqRm0ALJkYICIH3nxfpW59eG4n2udootV3Re3MxoPba07679mPJ4U46HaAhIZ6XhPlAuOGXloMfYaMwMDA1cCsipRE27IuqvIlsZsdjlzMvR49AdPE+3dY4f3NmNRD4ccri+N1H0QnA7r"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8041","langCode":"vi","question":"GUhNr9Y0D2FLFbviX2GwX9itvMPsFyDPGRqv9iwHOw9Yu9nqLZDffuJkuSxZ5e1SVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["operate on","own up","show up","note down"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQU+n9GpPLDkVCFCz6xBF9pIOvTHBdXJ5tqk/LDYpNPd46rp++FYIrYAMIhfFeFVwT5xOV5rufLcuR8RQiFwd9VsJwB9FV7qnqWVASgVWlS2HmAOqXC18pnfgHmxBNKCfqpAurQELQuHrlHe/Mol7Bmg0gjmTuhiuceGwM2TfvGbFpJBQlFkH+HWndtcGlSn/i2Li4ESh9xAjovtLS2KPRpBctDvrtBAiqAAhrtu7Rcjp/r3CGqNEyCqSih8sFVmgv782Sk7S9s7d35YnHTn5TSvkWD8IqCimBaDR13Rh9Y8WJohH7Wm345AswE3iqBf6bSoV837VW4Bc+O+iiozIG2zfIZKp1S8tuo+TZqDLc002s6XmNWc1VOedvExX7s4gShG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8042","langCode":"vi","question":"Wg+Idl/R+8RoE42H6hUkEeoTHjMjuY5vqo36uEAHVSOdFQZ7qHntKEE90JVn88WhXbZTvmUpB+dZuPlbIo+2SFSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["keep/in with","kick/out","talk/over","lay/into"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQzYwTBnoDietnKx5AhXUDdS5dPyDpar0HsyorU6nyHaepksNkYhjMzbAW+5+pYRd6Y0kFORgvHdRCIc03XlL+xrsUr6uhqLaGZo/DYCEPX80T6v7p5lPb4F8dKhcvaAYI1cP8sv98AYhwUzb18GRvNXE2H/7aKKUwohbcMcwqkub6ddKYbg5YrGjiUmAO0TE1pnqWfi6RJviZI3WnUXUaC7rmo2Hsslx9zwVOT8fMDIQ8b4PXA2t54L9uJbpmcSbf5I3N6I5mPTmDw2HfCGm+HJfhzP0yqGPqp9Xe7vKD/vvRjgmRkCpe08Qn+Nqr/Y5alORdu93svhJeJi9Qg7VwXv16T9Jm0A3AkLqVydL9aiqUkPMlpuIVruSwYKQ+DuBOfbWUQsMAaLcwYfnEzsb2ak38ACsmNaYUCdGXmY8CUl5lyFBxsqhDr6kXeAC2NyG8VUtc8Mz8EvWVsifj9BKtBQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8043","langCode":"vi","question":"SNFwdUIy08Y6sY/4v8ncI7h3PaCuLMiZ2pyywu+QGBF7V9U3UOCqqHbasGT2HRR9","answers":["look into","make up for","think over","look up to"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQjORT2w8PiXdcQVMLnWMuBI0BzFuHYPu+jZKE5yvTrQa9Ui86YinwkfKg8DG+sk6WI2BxiV2v3a3IHA2ZIE3cMundjmBoz+PctOWNWisNdWJxAnHuN0KgvDLHTDP32lb2qZrxulyvBXxNvtjq3uHLmNW0rQTNKIMx0T9LJ3LDXxWZoboHcSgJZUDIKeSey8ZRz9MnHKTFUFsAFrFGQ3CLm7CyTEq1X1Xwzzeb9DAfL4TYuLgRKH3ECOi+0tLYo9GkFy0O+u0ECKoACGu27tFyOk1AIBn3/nLVr6wch+4m5dcTd7t5rN2kk4Sz8YfHANPXCASXtiCrPxbgRGqWWn8lKUa5L/yuV+mkl9p8mLcgEtE0FP1Mi+xuNgGn6EP3Rc28khurMCGKuMNKgP9GZDQYLEwbUHMCVmX4RsoSr839h+1PCHDdYA06kfws/F7B/sA/y3oA6UVhA41lfsPbFtAAwg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8044","langCode":"vi","question":"hRevVMShvTr6tR17wC3XT8cb1asIpIdIwJuCqH0/TBy0KfOT6xJ0GJRAVrYl9v+Y27Krz1kXdz22TqdA8S3BQlSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["nodded off","put up to","queered up","run across"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQrJuZp3xNtBs10DIk9i8e+/hCxmSspKBTTrJsQy6R+TqrTHzTmeyTAsxbbffuu64s4dek6FDInI2DJvlGlYTwtWw8fNDPcXV2qN/o/mwck63o21l4+SimbaLyBtGRrdb+EIaWQeXcXP5tKhcHPz1N8clMvJZBmjiweHD6d9pMOuqhSUTuxPkZsJU0JAycN5VnDa9w8lyUHAOJrr2CoxsFGHHDlSatyWaWSyBmFdMGVmRxxWJbrPPqjknkuFH2tBGfLPccv+B1/RHL62hqcj20ETGI2osr7RoTlbTx36AeUJqTeQUqLL+B+io+3X4YLjnMzBh98kukf6yoIz1TkDIg5IbseZpvA2vYms/hXb9ts8070RWW91AMVtMPK2ECfH6Cd5vkJHCcu0FIwcVkdvkbNXfCPaOhm28H89D1ZluTuyI\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8045","langCode":"vi","question":"rU+PCXkctDqxpBxB/1dYxaMobFhJX/VAZDsDgNut/VeVIu/SNy4FHFkzfuJmIQHLVnYeNAmu3tiNrTL98O3EIw\u003d\u003d","answers":["keep on","ride on","read on","run after"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQMnylEYXQ5BkfOB9uQukYtqcpVbisMa0cgR0DF+a6R/l+zM7PsU4wi+KAiOOPnevtM0vpbKUBcqjnMmbu8Asy2gsxoCIBUBW2WmLI0/6faJZaaFEetSkXhshm7prVjwy4CyXuIxB+u8wTRnM/GA/jQz+a5uCciJNgpy1+c0MR9tHdzfJ5kZ+GYfhWJq6mG/tase6fA8629TMXsxDgm1kWBpsqbsX/fivt0OQHdD0PoLwhvaIoZUenbHSAcwdc/IHDbgp6Juz+TG076Y+vrdkQSd7hFLIjy1OhiGn0CdPIEJ2Irt5efnyTaIe0S7ziHftp71n00OQ0OmBS/FAaT+8wI5ehcQk3rpAJs7wCIEUWFPb8M7G4RPPXBd3yfNjKfzgP"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8046","langCode":"vi","question":"G6XG7ombU2TN4xTl62JO9NDraSzL/Htuk83XcCJz+hglQCJdW5jdORvxoELSz3uw","answers":["get in on","get behind","fall behind","wash up"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQsFD6XP4C/SvJPYW+sfnYws+yEKAMjsB4psFSyRKsxCRvsY2qgCSSD4V71k0q6bnznuysOJqA1CvWAjKpaJLCOrfgVKHrmh/Onw/oFsew92P/cwjFuiJHH9witU5ejeuu8Wa2AODV3yTYwFZfLUuFPgkf6T+VAezFKDfFdrlM2vQ15R2hInBZpiNyjVUen0Egw/jCeLSL/S125jkYuEXE9ds1cryrOsDfPue9vWxjTL73UaIco2wXAlxhl8A5yOZk34l3s2to9yRVG5X0lEvgzdKACVTgbWdrD8PD5McFsyW8PZcVN4HAQSRd9RLde6DUsZldfRQtvfxeibUZGjiLvR59WOCSY6hCnuWm2b6RIys\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8047","langCode":"vi","question":"ro/7DANSc8JCjarCoUcJRwl1iTDgPYV1KAB/H8i0Eb3/N4eRq6CcHrAClj/Yy26M","answers":["run out of","set upon","bear out","set aside"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQjlswzvnh6D3GFwqRRAytV9FXSxodKyWb2Zv1N3L6mqEN2srRmKVG+KsimToOn2GW2WXTAWYUJ4CC6eMtlSL2Uoko7LDq/Ys/dBE501iLWqPaEq7nNhRcOTnlPzMmSOiV8CraG0UNtmKgU/s7U6DimurwK3H+Y9sHnyDCTMi4Y9eeDXwvzv9n1nXQ3LtzGgxaXB28SbtFRIY9F8jR2gTEYCXXVY8Hem7Ca2jycAEPGvlNfXTVmKbemo5bZlUX8C4zOd6NylZrMdlAbSnPKUKrdirGe/8oE12887z8rwQclEdf5DV5cvGSqYoqy5rfXRkq1+BG2fbpOJcfBRPjGtiK9trfQ02SNRN3IjT4x7eta/zfCaCKGTr/Zcjv2sB9ezS+KMKwtqa+1dUppTlMKfrTHx/2iH48LCGqe21II2nOPGE\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8048","langCode":"vi","question":"0F96hkMEo9wVktoh/V4L/A23q9pD6Twe5bEz1G+/juRVcghLqppIVrH9VmPQXZmvYYfdJIgdQQZD54eU1Z+D9Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["saw through","slept in","speeded up","settle on"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQr07tofe0NftVKdNf+7VMhprWMN/rrmjfZtn1NJbwhjDZsep/og0r/k+CtLW1owGcXq9L1GY+OUSKlHxUn+RYtTSiIXpn9s2ScKHJDCptive7RNZraYoCXWfB2HH3RdasFCp9fNP+6eUVufdPWmPT5CJ0xzX/ibw66xl7Y0+/JLXXBcnvViqow+8UKdO/w7nppyx73dmR/S8IiQGWQ3lH4xMaoVwQvBgA31AGP4VUcnO2LEjMwfdttwA2pvBHd39vLW7k+L4ImcBE9E8gOQ1HwAL4jxwcA91Yr/l+xUQ7kWGHHp44/7b+XP4L4q/r5BlEeGKUHjL5WodKbfNtyuistlThQd3Vk4vx53D0UZNM21KDkNimxbxCriTh2kZ6otCQMIO/5P2goJ/vWKEXAHOrtIf93D6I8EXPKSNY7O9jmqnrWw+imSj+iFVtPwnAMryFo2NAcm0uN/nYrl4X1K0s7UsKROxYQp94r3HZD3CI2MOtX5NbxZBffJsVjjhGTYFxcFPA63kta8NXqhzE4pbCVHEt6xutxtsjEX0pPbix1MQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"8","id":"8049","langCode":"vi","question":"hPHneGwg+N0414Yr1XUT97/GTn3joSbMht+LbQ5GjZ2wKnmATTEB5YXhdBsiUUxy","answers":["pairs up with","gives up","stands for","gears up for"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"hUgsxvY78aMpQiv5MGhoBcwYhDsmQiq/zIoq5opTjRCFdrUP4lChTVcazFwky0NQk/cucVyjRicCoTmXwQHZrjXYrEGNZAt3iVDbpqeT5AvJUSF56So0UmXqLSJKpMAEE+r+6eZT2+BfHSoXL2gGCNXD/LL/fAGIcFM29fBkbzVxNh/+2iilMKIW3DHMKpLmpm+BtwKwtA+soXvi+T/4xxYvzLyeX+m8/cWH5yz3YpEJ2gj3aw14QKu3PtV3dZAeyScP2WvLXVpu4ETsgloiFWnEyCyuI4V/DErpfLxIdlQzXow2TXm30/tk9qG3M9bJlGA6dZQqAgCFHfomIDZnU8izdM6RRL2GCBaWlKV0pRbME1qh0S917E3Gvu5kOed2qo0SIgMcVcjRD7ZxvfOcqy8thFUqWazm01r5gnfqqvHnYARY+LV5Md4HfCnQh/bA7eK8Okrl8uZYLjQ0RCpGA4RvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"}]